Guide to the Archives of Irish America County Societies Collection AIA.003
Tamiment Library / Wagner Archives
- XXI. Mayo, 1924-2006
  - Mayo Gaelic Football Club of Greater New York Annual Dinner Dance, 2000, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Mayo Men's Committee for the Election of O'Dwyer - Joseph and Impellitteri: Contributions, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Assocation of New York Meeting Minutes, Jan 4, 1924 - Apr 12, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Assocation of New York Meeting Minutes, May 10, 1927 - Dec 9, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Assocation of New York Meeting Minutes, Jan 31, 1931-Dec 12, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Assocation of New York Meeting Minutes, Jan 23, 1934-Dec 10, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Assocation of New York Meeting Minutes, Jan 14, 1936-Jul 12, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Assocation Diamond Jubilee, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Assocation of New York Annual Ball, 1965-1988 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Mayo Men's Patriotic and Benevolent Assocation of New York Annual Fall Dance and Ball and Dinner-Dance, 1975-1978 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Mayo Society of New York Annual Ball and Dinner, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Mayo Society of New York Annual Ball and Dinner, 1994, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Mayo Society of New York Annual Ball and Dinner, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Mayo Society of New York Annual Ball and Dinner, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Mayo Society of New York Annual Ball and Dinner, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Mayo Society of New York Annual Ball and Dinner, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Mayo Society of New York Annual Ball and Dinner, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Mayo Society of New York Annual Ball and Dinner, 2004 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Mayo Society of New York Annual Ball and Dinner, 2006 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Mayo Society of New York: By-Laws, Correspondence, 1992, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Mayo Society of New York Hibernians of the Year, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Mayo Society of New York Michael Davitt and America, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Mayo Society of New York Newsletter, 1999, 2006-2009 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Mayo Society of Philadelphia 94th Annual Ball, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- XXII. Meath, 1996
  - The Meath Association, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- XXIII. Monaghan, 1977-1993
  - Monaghan Football Club of New York, 1977, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- XXIX. Offaly, 1977-1999
  - County Offaly Association of New York Inc.: Anniversary Dinner Dance, 1985-1987 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - County Offaly Association of New York Inc: Annivesary Dinner Dance, 1988-1996 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - County Offaly Association of New York Inc.: Annual Banquet, 1997-1999 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - County Offaly Association of New York Inc.: Annual Dinner Dance, 1982, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - County Offaly Association of New York Inc.: Annual Dinner Dance, 1978-1984 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Offaly Social and Athletic Club: Annual Dances, 1938, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Photograph: Hurling Team: Champions 1925-1928 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- XXV. Roscommon, 1931-2001
  - County Roscommon Society Constitution and By-laws, 1948, 1960, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Corporation Papers, 1951-1966 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1953-1987 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Financial: Auditor's Report, 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Financial: Cancelled Cheques, 1939-1959 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Financial: Cash Disbursement Account Book, Jan 1954-Sep 1965 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Financial: Cash Disbursement Account Book, Jun 1965-Feb 1974 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Financial: Cash Disbursement Account Book, Mar 1974-Dec 1989 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Financial: Cash Disbursement Account Book, Jan 1991-Jan 1994 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Financial: Check Books, 1947-1956 (Box 11a)
  - Financial: Chemical Bank Account, 1975-1977 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Financial Correspondence St. Patrick's Night Annual Ball, 1949-1950 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Financial Correspondence St. Patrick's Night Annual Ball, 1951-1953 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1952-1953 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1961 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Financial Correspondence, 1962 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Financial Correspondence: St. Patrick's Night Annual Ball, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Financial: Dinner-Dance Accounts, 1974-1976 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Football Club Fall Dinner-Dance, 1994-1995, 2000-2001 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Histories, 1961-1976 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Installation of Officers, 1968, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Membership Dues, 1960-1967 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Membership Dues, 1968-1977 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Membership Dues, 1974-1977 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Membership: Monthly Letters, 1973, 1983-1987 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Minutes, Jul 16, 1931-Dec 31, 1945 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Minutes, Jan 1, 1946-Dec 31, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Minutes, Jan 1, 1953-Dec 31, 1954 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Minutes, 1955 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Minutes, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Minutes, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Minutes, 1958 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Minutes, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Minutes, 1960 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Minutes, 1961 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Minutes, 1962, 1984 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1972-1986, undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Reunion Dinner-Dance, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - St. Patrick's Ball, 1964-1976 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - St. Patrick's Ball, 1977-1980 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - St. Patrick's Ball, 1981-1986 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - St. Patrick's Celebration and Reunion Dinner-Dance, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - St. Patrick's Dinner-Dance, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Stationery, 1980s (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Yearbook, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Yearbook, 1984-1985 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Photographs: Dinner-Dance, 1950s-1970s (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Photographs: Dinner-Dance, 1970s-1980s (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Photographs: Reunion Dinner-Dance, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Photographs: Social and Welfare Leagues, Inc. St. Patrick's Ball, Hotel Ritz Carleton (Panorama,framed), Mar 16, 1946 (Box 13a, Folder 1)
- XXVI. Sligo, 1963-2007
  - Football Club of New York Annual Dinner Dance, 1990, 1996, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Ladies Social and Benevolent Assocation Golden Jubilee Dinner Dance, 1963 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association 85th Anniversary Program, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association, Inc.: Anniversary Dance, 1991-1993 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association, Inc.: Annual Ball, 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association, Inc.: Annual Ball, 1986-1987 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association, Inc.: Annual Ball, 1988-1990 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association, Inc.: St. Patrick's Day Dinner Dance, 1994, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Men's Social and Benevolent Association, Inc.: St. Patrick's Day Dinner Dance, 2000-2001, 2007 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Sligo Supporters Club of New York Celebration Banquet, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Publication: Sligo in New York: The Irish from Co. Sligo: 1849-1991. John T. Ridge. County Sligo Social and Benevolent Assocation. New York. 1991. (Box 14, Folder 10a)
- XXVII. Tipperary, 1914-2004
  - Annual Ball, 1960, 1983-1985 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Annual Ball, 1987-1990 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Annual Ball, 1992-1995 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Annial Ball, 1996-1997 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Annual Ball, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Annual Ball, 2002 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Annual Ball, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Hurling Club Annual Dinner Dance, 1987, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Ladies Social and Benevolent Association Ball Programme (photocopy), Apr 4, 1914 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - N&B Association Annual Ball, 1965-1966, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - N&B Assocation Annual Ball, 2005, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Old I.R. A. Commemorative Calendar, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 4a)
- XXVIII. Tyrone, 1983-2002
  - Pipe Band 50th Anniversary Dinner Dance, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Pipe Band Advertising Contract, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Society Annual Dinner Dance, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- XXIX. Waterford
- XXX. Westmeath
- XXXI. Wexford, 2004-2007
  - Annual Dinner Dance Anniversary Celebration, 2004, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- XXXII. Wicklow